[Curtis] Previously
on Motorheads...
Could be you.
Things are tight around here.
What about restoring old cars?
Not your worst idea.
[Brooke] I didn't know
that you knew Curtis Young.
Does he have a girlfriend?
- I like you.
- Things are just complicated.
[Sam] I've been meaning
to ask you about Marcel.
He was in hospital and
his dad was unreachable.
He may not be perfect.
but he's all I got.
[Zac] I wanna learn to race.
- And I need you to teach me.
- I can't.
You said I could
be good at racing.
- I want your help.
- It's time to get you a car.
[engines rev]
[engines accelerating]
[spectator] Whoo!
[crowd cheering]
[rock music playing]
[engine revs]
Is Mikey serious right now?
- About what?
- Come on.
He's racing that piece of junk?
Never underestimate the car.
You never know what's
under the hood.
Uh. she's ready to roll.
Yeah. Good luck
against this thing.
You don't know?
Know-Know what?
You're up. kid.
[Zac] What?
That's what you wanted. right?
Yeah. but. like. right now?
Right now.
You know. my arm's
getting tired.
- Sorry.
- [music stops]
[engine starts]
[pants]
Is this thing fast?
- Guess you're about to find out.
- [engine revs]
[engine revving]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
[tires squeal]
[laughs]
[sighs]
Damn.
[crowd cheering]
- [Zac] I thought I had him.
- It wasn't even close.
This thing didn't have
enough under the hood.
Oh. so it's the
car's fault again?
Give him the keys.
- What?
- Give him the keys.
[Zac] Why?
'Cause it's his car now.
Yo. where are you going?
I made a mistake.
But-But you said that
you were gonna teach me.
Yeah. well. I'm
rethinking that offer.
I didn't know I was racing
tonight. I wasn't ready.
Well. unfortunately. I had
to see that for myself.
So this was a test?
Look. call it what you want.
kid. You just don't have it.
Oh. and. uh. now
you owe me a car.
[phone buzzes]
["Fall In Line"
playing on radio]
It's not the
screwdriver's fault.
[Caitlyn] I've been trying to make this
old part fit. but it's not working.
Been waiting over a week
for the new one to come in.
And we both know how much
you love waiting. [sighs]
Also this is a socket
wrench. not a screwdriver.
Stick to driving.
this is my lane.
Yeah. [exhales sharply]
[wrenching clinking]
[sighs] Maybe...
driving isn't my thing either.
Really not in the mood
to pump your ego. dude.
I'm not asking you to pump my ego.
I'm telling you I'm not ready.
Neither is the car.
Not yet. But you're gonna fix the
car. and I still won't be ready.
Oh. my God. You
lost one race. dude.
Why are you holding
up two fingers?
I lost tonight.
You raced. Against who?
I didn't get his
name. Gold teeth.
Whose car did you race?
[sighs] It was Ray Young's.
- [chuckles]
- [stammers] At least it was...
before and...
during the race. but I lost
it to the gold tooth guy.
So you lost Ray's car.
Amazing. Incredible.
Good job. Zac.
You know Logan said that Ray's someone
you don't wanna owe anything to?
Do you owe Ray a car now?
No. no. Okay?
It was just some junky car
that didn't matter to him.
He was training me
because Logan said no.
- [sighs]
- [wrench clinking]
That's all over now. okay?
And-And this...
it's over for me
at least. [mutters]
- Come on. Zac.
- I'm sorry. Cate.
You were right to doubt me.
I just don't have it.
[somber hip-hop music playing]
When's the last time
you washed that thing?
That long. huh?
So how you doing. son?
Fine.
Yeah?
Yeah. you don't...
you don't seem fine.
Matter of fact. uh. if I'm being honest.
you seem kind of angry all the time.
Kind of opposite of fine.
Well. you told me
to be angry. so...
Yeah.
After your mother died. I told
you to grieve at your own pace.
It's okay to be angry.
But that was months ago.
- All right. so my own pace.
- [trunk closes]
Yeah. [sighs] No. I just...
I worry you're. uh. taking your anger out
on people who don't really deserve it.
- [music stops]
- Wait. who are you talking about?
New kids.
Christian Maddox's kids?
Yeah. I know their mom.
Right. so they cried to their mommy
and then their mommy cried to you.
- Is that what happened?
- [chuckles] No.
We just reconnected recently.
Look. this dumb rivalry you got going with
her son. it feels familiar. All right?
- It's probably not gonna end well.
- For him.
Is that the only reason
why you came out here?
"Hey. son. Stop being
the school bully."
No. I actually. uh. wanted to tell
you something. um... [smacks lips]
I had a meeting with
Alicia's dad. Bruce Whitaker.
Why?
He made us an offer.
Us?
Yes. You and me.
We're in this
together. It's just us.
Bandit Technology made us an offer to
buy all of our real estate in town.
All of it.
It's a good offer.
I'm sure it is.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime offer.
And. uh. you laughed
in his face. right?
I said yes.
[Marcel] This thing
belongs in a museum.
Oh. red numbers are bad. right?
Yep. Shop's not doing so great.
Have you. uh. heard
from Curtis today?
[clicks tongue] Uh. he said he was helping
his dad with something this morning.
Oh. the boat?
- I don't know.
- [door opens]
What are you guys doing on
my old college computer?
[clicks tongue] We are
importing your books into it.
- What college did you go to?
- I didn't.
It was a graduation gift.
To use if I went to college.
Kinda like getting
a wedding gift.
calling off the wedding.
and keeping the gift.
Why are you here so early?
I'm checking on my car.
[clicks tongue] Two
more weeks. Minimum.
[sighs] You really gotta
upgrade this place.
We talked about this.
You're spending a lot
more than you're making.
Didn't need a fancy
computer to tell me that.
What. this thing's
fancy? [chuckles]
Sorry. it's. uh.
it's timeless. So...
I might have some income coming
in soon anyway. thanks to you.
Wha... Thanks to me?
No. thanks to Cate.
Remember your big classic
car restoration idea?
- Yeah.
- Well... [sighs]
...I might've hooked a big fish.
Apparently. Bruce Whitaker from
Bandit has an insane collection.
Doesn't surprise me.
Yeah. I heard he has
the original Batmobile.
And the A-Team van.
Unconfirmed.
Well. I'm about to get
you that confirmation.
'cause I'm headed over
there now. You wanna come?
Uh. I gotta go help set up the Wade's
Diner booth at the car auction.
It's a shame your dad's chili
won't be there this year.
That's my favorite part.
Yeah. mine too.
- Well. I'll see you guys there.
- Okay. bye.
- Here you go.
- All right. let's go.
Oh. I can't. I'm meeting
Mom for breakfast.
But. uh. you should ask Zac.
He's being kind
of weird with me.
All the more reason to ask him.
- He's into Whitaker's daughter.
- Hmm?
He's into Whitaker's daughter.
Maybe use that angle.
Zac. my man!
You. me. Whitaker estate?
- Let's do this.
- What?
I'm going to see their car
collection. You're coming with.
Uh. no thanks.
Uh. his. uh. daughter
might be there.
So?
I don't know. Cate told
me to use that angle.
- Great. Just go with him.
- And do what?
I'm the guy that doesn't
know the difference
between a monkey wrench and
a screwdriver. remember?
Socket wrench.
- And you can be his helper.
- Yeah. my. uh. general helper.
You can carry the tools or
just flirt with his daughter.
Might even get to see the
original Batmobile. A-Team van.
- Really?
- Well. unconfirmed.
No promises.
Let's go!
[sighs]
[Sam] What are you gonna get?
You know. I'm deciding between... [sighs]
...unhealthy and super unhealthy. [chuckles]
But I would actually like to order
soon so we can get back to the shop.
No.
What do you mean. "No"?
We're gonna take our
time and enjoy the meal.
There's a whole other world
outside the auto shop.
Yeah. a complicated one.
Wanna talk about it?
Not really. [sighs]
How's Kiara?
[clicks tongue] She is in the
Poconos with her boyfriend.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Uh. this is my mom.
- Mom. Brooke.
- [chuckles] Hi.
Hi. So you guys ready
to order something?
- Yes.
- Couple of minutes.
Sorry.
Um. actually. have you seen
Curtis? Has he been here?
No. no. I wish.
I-I haven't seen him.
- But I'll give you guys a few minutes.
- Okay.
"I wish"? What does that mean?
Does Curtis have
a secret admirer?
[scoffs] Not so secret. I guess.
I was just gonna
ask about Curtis.
I told him that we
should just be friends.
Huh.
Is that what you really want?
I don't know. I don't know.
I really and truly
don't know. I just...
The only time that I feel like
I actually know what I'm doing
is when I'm in the shop
working on Dad's car.
[breathes deeply] Hmm.
I think I know what you need.
- I'm gonna show you something today.
- Show me what?
My car.
I know what your car looks like.
No! That's my car outside!
The red one on the trailer.
Wait. you used to have an RX-7?
[chuckling] No. I used
to have that RX-7.
You're sure?
Yes. this... [chuckles]
...this is it.
This is my first car.
You're sure?
I mean. see that stripe?
- That was me.
- Huh.
Dangerous yet tasteful.
I loved this car.
I guess it's in town
for the auction.
You should buy it.
- [chuckling] What? No way.
- Yes way.
- What would I do with an RX-7?
- Drive it very fast.
You know that's not me.
I bet it used to be.
- I didn't say that.
- Oh. you didn't have to. I can see it.
- [chuckles]
- See what?
Oh. I can totally see it.
You're looking at that car
like it's full of secrets.
Things you don't
want me to know.
- [chuckling]
- Am I wrong? Tell me I'm wrong.
What does the car know?
Did you race it?
No.
No. come on. let's go eat.
And then I wanna
show you something.
You totally used to race it.
[groans]
Man... look at this place.
Hey. you okay?
Been kind of quiet.
Still upset about the
whole racing thing?
- [scoffs]
- Me not training you?
No. I'm over that.
Was a bad idea.
- Logan Maddox? Bruce Whitaker.
- [Logan] Hey.
- This is my nephew. Zac.
- Hi.
Hey. um. i-is Alicia here? We have
lockers next to each other at school.
Ah. Yeah. she's out there
on her horse somewhere.
Why don't you go say hi?
Uh. yeah. okay. Bye.
It's good to finally meet you.
We've met actually.
- What?
- Uh. last year in town.
I must've not
known that was you.
Obviously I've heard
the name from. uh...
- Get that a lot.
- Oh. yeah. no. don't-don't worry.
I know a lot of people must.
uh. hold that against you.
But. uh. not me. I'm actually...
I'm actually a bit of a fan.
Oh. Of mine?
[chuckles] Of the story.
Uh. the mystery.
- Want my autograph?
- [chuckles]
She's beautiful.
Had her as long
as I can remember.
What's the book value?
Not enough. if you ask me.
You ready to see
my toy collection?
This ain't it?
- Hey.
- [Alicia] Hey.
Who's this?
Lexi.
[both chuckle]
Are you about to take her out?
I just got back. Just
cooling her down.
So you're just. like.
walking in circles?
Yeah. pretty much.
Can I walk in circles with you?
- Yeah.
- [chuckles] Okay.
[Lexi nickers]
Here with your uncle?
Uh. yeah. yeah.
He's. like. starting this.
like. car restoration side gig.
- Uh-uh.
- So he's here to check out your dad's...
Toy collection?
- That's... That's what he calls his cars.
- [chuckles] Oh.
Even though he has an
actual toy collection.
Wait. like... like
Star Wars and stuff?
- Mm-hmm. [chuckles]
- Hmm.
What's he call that?
- Uh. his vintage collectibles. [chuckles]
- [chuckles] Okay.
You don't wanna see his cars?
Uh. okay. well I did. actually.
But... I don't know. I guess
I just wanted to see you more.
If that's okay.
Unless he actually does
have the Batmobile.
'cause if he does. I'ma
have to see you later.
- [chuckling] Oh!
- Sorry. yeah.
- Love Batman. so...
- [Alicia chuckles]
What's all this for?
- Ingredients.
- For what?
- I have an idea.
- Oh. yeah?
You Gordon Ramsay now?
Well. today's the
annual car auction.
So?
Thought maybe you could
make your famous chili.
- Why?
- Tradition.
It's always a bigger hit
than the actual cars.
Nobody cares.
I do.
I mean. Logan even
brought it up.
I-I'm sure a lot of people care.
[sighs. scoffs]
If you don't want to. fine.
I'll do it.
[scoffs]
Why are you doing it
that way with a fork?
- This is how I do it.
- Yeah. well. it's wrong.
It's my version.
Well. your version is
wr... Okay. you know what?
Step back. step back.
First off. no fork. right?
- Chef's knife. always.
- Yeah.
Give it a light tap.
Cut it lengthwise.
If the core inside is dry. you cut it
out 'cause it's gonna be bitter. right?
Then what did I teach you?
Three fingers. all right?
Middle finger in front.
Use it as a guide.
Chop all the way through.
- Nice. Well. I'll do the celery.
- No. no. no. no. I got the celery.
You know what. just give
me some room. all right?
Why are you holding that spoon?
In case you need me
to hand it to you.
[chuckles]
Good thinking.
This is cool.
[sighs] This is my spot.
What do you do here?
Nothing.
- [chuckles] Nothing?
- I sit here and do nothing.
Everyone has a spot.
You. Logan.
He stole this spot from me.
Even Curtis has a spot.
Overlooking the town
by the waterfall.
Sounds like a make-out spot.
He's not like that.
What's holding you back?
What we have. working on Dad's
car together. it feels...
like. too good to mess up.
So maybe you should finish
the car and figure it out.
Come on. come sit with me.
And do nothing?
And do nothing.
Geez. Pentagon-level security.
You think it's a bit much?
Guess it depends on
what you have in there.
Well. when you see my toys.
you're gonna understand why.
You're looking away. right?
- [keypad beeps]
- Yeah.
- [beeps]
- [lock clicks]
[Bruce] Illuminate!
[Logan] Illuminate?
From Demolition Man?
That's where I got it from.
So. what do you think?
This little baby.
direct from the bar.
was Dean Martin's.
No shit.
Hold up. is that...
Eleanor.
[chuckles] Impressive.
You got three of my top
four all-time cars in here.
Which one's missing?
I drove here in it.
Of course.
Hey. uh. where's the...
Batmobile? Another room?
What?
Or the A-Team van?
You don't have those. do you?
Maybe some day.
I almost had the Knight
Rider car. but I got outbid.
And that's never
gonna happen again.
And that's the car
I want restored.
'68 E-Type. [sighs]
Looks beautiful.
What's wrong with it?
You tell me.
Oh. I see the problem.
Your steering wheel's
on the wrong side.
It's gonna be tricky to fix.
- Kidding. [chuckles]
- [chuckles]
Needs. uh. molding
on the chromework.
Shut lines aren't true.
Looks okay. but if you wanna
do this the right way...
I'd replace the dash.
It's easier said than
done. but I bet it rattles.
It does.
She could use a new coat.
And that is a gorgeous
Moto-Lita steering wheel
with a terrible finish.
And it's the wrong size.
Got a hairline crack
on the windshield.
That'll be tough
with this shape.
Well. can you fix it?
I can fix anything.
I'll have them deliver
it to your shop.
Just like that?
It's gonna take some time
to get the original parts.
- and. uh. hunting down that dash...
- Just put it back to the way it was.
You'll think it's 1968.
"De-lluminate"!
Is that a word?
I don't think so.
No. it's not a word.
- Just let her take it. [chuckles]
- Ah. is she gonna bite me?
Only if she doesn't like you.
[both chuckling]
I guess she likes you.
Please tell me she bit Harris.
[both chuckle]
So. um. are you going
to the auction later?
Uh. no. not this year.
Lexi and I have a pretty
big competition today. so...
- A race?
- Uh. jumping.
- Oh. I'm impressed.
- Mmm. don't be.
I never win.
Well. do you like it?
Yeah. I love it.
Especially this part.
you know. the training.
The losing part is
never. ever fun.
My dad expects me to get out
there and win. you know. so...
I don't know. It's tough loving
something that you're not great at.
Yeah. Yeah. I get that.
Well. uh. I should
probably get back to Logan.
- Something I said?
- No. no.
Uh. but hey. good
luck at your meet.
and if I wasn't working the
Wade's Diner booth at the auction.
um... I'd be there.
No. don't worry about it.
Harris is coming. so...
Okay. Bye.
[Brooke] You missed a spot.
I like the new stripe.
Me too.
Thanks for coming.
- I didn't want to.
- Yeah. you couldn't resist my charm.
I need your help. I'm
looking for my shirt.
I'm a little
vulnerable right now.
You sounded sad on the phone
and I didn't like that. okay?
That's the only reason I'm here.
Harris. what happened?
Alicia's dad bought us out.
What do you mean?
Well. you know all those buildings
in town with our name on them?
Yeah?
We're selling them
all to Bandit.
- Why?
'Cause it's a once-in-a-lifetime
offer. That's why.
[scoffs] Okay. so you'll
make a lot of money.
I don't care about that.
What do you care about?
Legacy.
[chuckles]
Is it a done deal?
Because if your legacy
means that much to you.
then maybe you
should fight for it.
That's what I would do.
That's what you would do?
- Mm-hmm.
- With my legacy?
[chuckles] Harris.
Promise me that it's
really over this time.
Promise.
I'll forward you enough money
to get all those orders in.
Thanks. That'd be
really helpful.
I mean. it's better
than a horse. right?
Yeah. [chuckles] Yeah.
- [sighs]
- [chuckles]
[Bruce] She is pretty.
[chuckles]
What'd you say the
book value is again?
- I said "not enough."
- Is double enough?
She's not for sale.
Triple.
Should I keep going?
Thanks but...
never gonna happen.
[doors close]
You should buy that RX-7.
- [sighs]
- [chuckles]
Even if it's for no other reason
other than I can tell people
that my mom drives an RX-7.
[both chuckle]
So how'd this become your spot?
Well. I got a flat
tire back there.
and so I called a tow truck.
Why did you call a tow truck?
- Don't judge me.
- Did you not have a spare?
- No.
- Mom!
[chuckles] Do you wanna
hear the story or not?
Yeah. [chuckles]
Okay. so. the tow
truck doesn't come.
but this really
cute guy shows up.
[sighs] He was a bad boy.
Cocky.
He had a Top Banana
yellow Dodge Charger.
That's how you met Dad?
Yeah.
I mean. not officially. I knew
who he was and he knew of me.
But yeah. he had a spare.
And now every time
I come here. I...
I just know that things
are gonna work out.
- [sighs]
- Mmm.
You need a spot.
[chuckles] Can I
borrow this one?
[both chuckle]
No. This spot's getting
kind of crowded.
- You need your own spot.
- [chuckles]
Some place where you can just
get away from all the noise.
How do I find it?
You'll just know.
You know. when things
aren't going so great.
it'll be a place that
makes you feel safe.
A place where you
can just go and...
Do nothing?
[chuckles] Yeah.
- Let me give that thing a spin.
- No. I said no. dude. Quit asking.
- What. you think I'm gonna break it?
- I'm not interested in finding out.
But yes. I am fairly certain
that you would break it.
- Why. is it hard?
- Not really.
[Marcel] There's my dad.
- Hey.
Listen. why don't you get the
chili out of the truck. okay?
- I'm gonna put up my sign.
- What. you made a sign?
[Wade chuckles]
["Bar. Guitar. and a
Honky-tonk Crowd" playing]
[softly] Hey. Marcel. Psst.
Can I cut the line?
- Sure. Yeah.
- No. no. no.
You wait in line
like everybody else.
That's cold. Wade.
How was the Batmobile?
Would you please talk some sense into
Mom? Her old car is up for auction.
- [chuckles]
- The RX-7?
I thought that stripe
looked familiar.
She has to buy it. right?
- I'm not buying it.
- You should buy it.
You might be able to get a good deal.
I think the bidding starts at 8.500.
- I'm not buying it. [chuckles]
- Aw. come on.
I'll be right back.
- Buying or selling?
- [chuckles]
Neither. I just wanted
to be here today.
This event. it's one of the
things I love about the town.
What about you? You gonna bid?
- No.
- Oh.
Slight hesitation there.
Yeah. my daughter is
playing mind games with me.
She wants me to get into a time machine
and pretend that I'm cool again.
[chuckles]
Oh. uh. that reminds
me. I spoke to my son.
Told him to back off your kids.
Oh. Great.
Now he's gonna think
that my kids cried to me.
and I came running to you.
Yeah. I probably
shouldn't have done that.
- Probably not.
- [chuckles]
It's crazy though. right?
How familiar this is
to back in our day?
Two boys fighting over a girl.
That's literally every
high school in the world.
- Yeah. Good point.
- [chuckles]
- It's always good to see you. Sam.
- Mmm.
Oh. uh. whatever you're
thinking about bidding on.
- I think you should do it.
- Easy for you to say. You own the town.
Not anymore.
Here you go. man. Thanks
for coming to Wade's.
Three chilies.
We don't have chili.
- Yeah. you do.
- Nope.
- I saw the sign.
- No. we don't have chili. Edwin. okay?
Just go wait in that
really long line.
- Lame.
- You're lame.
Wait. What's Harris doing here?
He's allowed to be here.
No. no. it's just that Alicia
has a horse competition today.
- He should be there.
- They broke up.
No. they didn't.
And there's Alicia's dad.
Why is nobody there
for her today?
Wait. what do you mean.
they didn't break up?
I spoke to her a
couple of hours ago.
She said that Harris was
supposed to be there.
- Look at you! You're all professional.
- Yo. Where you been?
Oh. I was helping my
dad with our boat.
You have a boat?
- Sort of.
- [chuckles]
Hey. man. um...
Would you mind covering for me?
[chuckles] What I just.
like. serve chili?
Uh. we don't have chili.
- No. I saw the sign.
- Forget the sign.
- Thank you.
- Yeah. I guess.
- Thanks. dude.
- What. I just stand here and...
[Zac] Yeah. you'll
figure it out.
Hi. Uh. welcome to Wade's Diner.
We don't have chili.
I already asked.
- What are you doing here?
- I work here.
- Oh. Since when?
- Since. like. 20 seconds ago.
- [chuckles]
- I'm kidding. I'm covering for Zac.
Is that okay?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- All right. Okay.
Well. what can I get you?
Next up is this
beautiful Shelby Cobra!
We're gonna start the
bidding at $750.000.
I have $750.000.
Hey. can I talk to you?
You know Alicia's dad.
I do. I just... It'll
just take a minute.
[auctioneer] Nine
hundred thou... 900.000.
What's up?
Let's fight.
- Harris. I'm tired of fighting with you.
- No. no. no.
Let's fight for our name. Okay?
Forget the
once-in-a-lifetime offer.
We can get through this.
- Harris...
- Dad. It's all I have.
Please don't sell.
It's too late.
What?
The deal is signed.
I'm sorry.
I thought you said
we're in this together.
- We are in this together.
- Okay. Because Mom would have fought.
Till the very end. she always
fought. You remember that?
[Harris scoffs]
You gave up.
[auctioneer] One
million point three.
One million point three.
Going once. Going twice.
[auctioneer] Sold!
At $1.3 million!
- That's mine. That's mine now.
- Congrats.
That is mine.
Hey. you were close.
That was great.
[Curtis] All right.
Just a moment for the rest
of it. Uh. yeah. Thank you.
New job?
I'm. uh. covering
for your brother.
Have you been getting
any of my texts?
I was working on the boat.
Do you not get service
in your driveway?
Sorry.
Are you coming
back to the garage?
Uh... when?
Ever?
Of course. [sighs]
Wait. you didn't think I
was bailing on you. did you?
- I wasn't sure. so...
- [auctioneer] Next up! Item number 36.
This classic 1995 Mazda RX-7.
- [Curtis] So. did you end up fixing the...
- I'll... I'll be right back. Sorry.
Here you go.
So are you ready to learn
about the credit card machine?
- I've been waiting. Honestly.
- [chuckles] Yeah? Okay.
So you start right here
and hit this button.
This classic 1995 Mazda RX-7.
We're gonna start the bidding
at 8.500. Do I hear 8.500?
8.500 right there.
- Do I have 9.000?
- I can only go to 12.500.
- [auctioneer] 9.000 right here.
- Should be enough.
I sold the car for 6.000.
- It's a classic now.
- Do we have 9.500?
9.500 over here.
- This is exciting. [chuckles]
- It is exciting.
- Okay. Any more bids?
- Under ten grand?
- It's a steal.
- [auctioneer] 9.500. Going once.
And it's going twice.
10.000 over there.
Do we have 10.500?
10.500.
Do I have 11.000?
20.000!
- [auctioneer] 20.000.
- What the hell's he doing?
[auctioneer] ...going
once. Going twice.
- [gavel raps]
- [auctioneer] Sold for $20.000.
- What? I'm so sorry.
- [crowd applauds]
[Bruce] Thank you.
- Yo. What was that?
- Just adding to my toy collection.
- With a '95 RX-7?
- [sighs]
You can find ten of
those on eBay right now.
This one feels special.
Yeah. it was her first car.
Yeah. I heard about that.
I only buy cars
that have meaning.
That have a story.
And this one does.
I might lose the stripe
though. I don't like it.
[Logan sighs]
[audience applauding]
[no audible dialogue]
What are you doing here?
Oh. I thought you could
use a cheering section.
I was pretty loud out there.
- That was you?
- Yeah.
- Too loud for a horse show?
- No.
- [Zac chuckles]
- No. I liked it.
- Cool.
- Well. come on.
Yeah. Dude. you did
great out there.
- No. [chuckles]
- No. I'm serious. You killed it.
There you go.
Of course.
- Can I talk to you?
- Yeah. you want some chili?
Uh. no.
I mean. yes. but under the
circumstances. I think I should abstain.
What circumstances?
- I hate this.
- What's wrong?
My dad told me to talk to
you. so that's what I'm doing.
But I hate it.
You already said that.
What's happening?
- I feel like I got your hopes up.
- Oh. don't worry. sweetie.
It was a lot of money.
And let's be honest.
an RX-7 is not a practical
car for an ER nurse.
I'm actually kinda relieved.
No. you're not.
I am. Come on. I'll be fine.
Here. Want some chili?
I mean. there is a
really long line.
Hey. you don't have a
VIP pass with Marcel?
[chuckles] I wish.
[Wade] Hey. What is
this? What are you doing?
- Uh. nothing.
- Well. why are you taking the sign down?
You don't need a sign.
Look at that line.
Everyone knows where you are.
Okay. Put it back up.
- Uh. Dad...
- Now.
I-I can't.
It says "Wade's Diner". They...
They already have their own booth.
- So?
- So...
they don't even serve
chili over there.
Apparently. there's been
some confusion today.
and they have the
rights to the name.
My name.
I can't use my name?
Maybe we could just cross
out the "Diner" part.
Just go with "Wade's Chili"?
I can ask if that's okay.
This was all your idea.
Wh-Where are you going?
[Wade] Home.
But there's a lot of
people here for you.
[Lexi whinnies]
You and Lexi were the
best jumpers out there.
Fifth best.
Officially.
You didn't have to come.
Hmm. Someone did.
Yeah.
Well. my dad stopped showing up when
he realized I was never gonna win.
I guess...
I guess that's why
Harris isn't here too.
How do they know
you're not gonna win?
Well. the gap between the top
tier and the rest of us is...
is big.
I mean. I'm pretty good but...
I don't know. maybe
I just don't have it.
Just gotta work harder.
- [chuckles]
- No. no. I'm... I'm serious.
- Like. how many people are born great?
- Hmm.
Greatness comes from. like.
working harder than everyone else.
And you can always set
yourself up to win next time.
It's not that easy.
Nobody said it was.
But you... you love this.
And if you love something. you
should give it all you've got.
You shouldn't let anyone tell
you that you don't have it.
Hey. what's wrong?
I just had to make a friend do something.
and I feel really terrible about it.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Let's get out of here. Okay? I'll
make you feel better. I promise.
Are you and Alicia
still together?
Of course not.
Technically. we haven't had the
official chat yet. but that's not...
I can't do this anymore.
I deserve better than this.
Better than you. and...
Honestly. I think I like someone
else more than I like you.
Who?
[Curtis] Hey.
[scoffs]
[Curtis] All right. [sighs]
Uh. thanks. um. for
covering for Zac.
It was. uh... it
was interesting.
Especially that last
part. That was unexpected.
It wasn't what it seemed.
Seemed like a kiss.
- Yes. Yes. it was. I'm... I just...
- What? Was it like a dare. or...
No. Oh. no. Uh.
no. of course not.
No. I wouldn't... I
wouldn't. uh. do that to you.
I just. um...
was trying to make
a guy jealous. or...
maybe send a message.
[chuckles] What message?
That I'm moving on.
Oh.
Well. uh. if you ever wanna
make him jealous again.
I'm available.
Good to know.
- What you working on?
- Nothing.
Nothing?
Just sitting here.
First time ever.
I've seen you
sitting there before.
Yeah. but I'm always
working on something.
This is... different.
Mom took me to her spot today.
- My spot?
- I don't know.
She said that you
stole it from her.
- Can't keep spots.
- [chuckles]
You know. I think I found mine.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- Where?
- Right here. in this garage.
Like. no matter how
bad things seem.
when I'm in here. it just kind of
feels like everything's gonna work out.
[chuckles]
So. you know. no
pressure but. uh.
please keep the shop alive.
- Doing my best.
- I know.
But...
Mom's spot by the river
is always gonna be there.
And I know that this garage
won't be here forever.
I just...
I think I really need it.
while I'm lucky
enough to have it.
["All the Wild Horses"
playing on radio]
[exhales sharply]
Change of heart?
Probably won't agree
to this. but. uh...
I guess I'm willing to say
goodbye to her for. uh...
- five times book value.
- Done.
I was hoping you'd say no.
Please. take her
out once in a while.
So we have a deal?
Just one more
thing I need first.
[Sam chuckles]
What's this?
- What's it look like?
- You bought it?
Sort of.
First you stole my spot. and
now you bought my old car?
It's not for me. dummy.
Wanna go for a ride?
[thunder rumbling]
Hey!
That's my name.
That's my name!
[grunts]
[breathes heavily]
[sobbing]
[sighs]
["Twinkle" playing on speakers]
- Hey.
- [grunts]
Hi.
Where we at?
[grunts] I've been trying to force
some square pegs into round holes.
Can I give it a try?
Yeah. sure.
[music continues]
I was. uh. actually
thinking. um...
You know. maybe when
we're done with the car.
you and I could...
[Marcel] Hey. guys.
Hey. dude.
Can I hang out here?
Always.
Where's Zac?
[angle grinder whirring]
- [speaking indistinctly]
- [Zac] Hey!
No. Get out.
Look. you can't be
hanging around here. kid.
We gave it a shot. all right?
Just...
You just don't have it.
I think I do.
- Until it's the car's fault.
- No.
[sighs] Okay. look.
- I'm not gonna blame the car anymore.
- All right.
If I lose. it's because I
didn't work hard enough.
But I'm ready to focus.
and I'm ready to get better at
this. and I know I have it in me.
and we both know it's
running through my veins.
Think you could win in that?
She's a piece of junk.
Never underestimate
the car. right?
Never know what's
under the hood.
Pop the hood.
[Zac] Dude. [chuckles]
[Ray] She's a sleeper car.
She's a beast.
- [chuckles]
- They'll never see you coming.
[rock music playing]
[music continues on radio]
So. how's it feel?
Like a time machine.
[chuckles]
All right. what are
you waiting for?
Open her up.
- [gear shifts]
- [engine roars]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm